silentauctionpro.com 2015-04-07

# Silent Auction Pro - Privacy Policy

Silent Auction Pro™ Privacy Policy 

There are differences in the privacy policies relating to the information stored in the Silent Auction Pro system; 

  * Privacy related to **Users** of the Silent Auction Pro system.
  * Privacy related to **Contacts** stored in the Silent Auction Pro system

**_Users_** are defined as persons who have created a Silent Auction Pro account and who are Members (or have been members) of Groups using Silent Auction Pro with a membership level of "Member" or higher. 

**_Contacts_** are defined as persons who have not created a Silent Auction Pro account and who's information has been entered by Users of Silent Auction Pro or who have created accounts only for the express purpose of purchasing tickets or online bidding. 

Differences in the privacy policy are called out below where the policy differs. 

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you create an account on our site. 

When ordering or creating an account on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. Parts of our site you may, however, visit anonymously. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To improve our website - (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

To process transactions  

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To send periodic emails  

> **_Users:_** The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

> **_Contacts:_** Contacts entered into the system will not be contacted by Silent Auction Pro except as is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 
> 
> **Note:** Silent Auction Pro provides the ability for Administrators of a Group to send emails to Contacts of that Group. This is not considered being contacted by Silent Auction Pro as the email is being initiated by and is under the control of the adminstrator sending the email and not Silent Auction Pro. 

### How do we protect your information?

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes  

> (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 
> 
> We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
